westwood.edu 2015-06-12

# Westwood College Privacy Policy

### General

Westwood College, Inc. (dba Alta Colleges) respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web sites, requests information, or responds to our promotions. To better protect your privacy we have provided this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Alta Colleges web sites, unless otherwise posted. Below is a list of sites that are covered by this privacy policy:

redstone.edu, westwood.edu, westwoodcollegecalifornia.com, westwoodcollegecolorado.com, westwoodcollegeillinois.com, westwoodcollegegeorgia.com, westwoodcollegetexas.com, westwoodcollegevirginia.com, westwoodinteriordesign.com, westwoodgamedsign.com, westwoodbusinessdegree.com, westwoodcriminaljustice.com, onlinewestwoodcollege.com, westwooddegreeonline.com, westwoodcollegesuccess.com, acceleratebywestwood.com, westwoodcollege.mobi, go.westwood.edu

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at information@westwood.edu. This policy covers only information collected through this Web site and does not cover information that may be collected within the Online Admission Center.

### Information you provide to us

Alta Colleges will collect personally identifiable information about you such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address. We will collect additional information such as your social security number, date of birth, ethnicity and emergency contact information when you register for our online admission center. We collect information that you provide to us for the following uses, unless otherwise stated:

  * We will use it to contact you and respond to your request for information. 
  * We may store and process the information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our web site and services. 
  * We will use this information to create an account for you when you register with our online admission center. 
  * To provide you access to your online account so that you may register for classes, update information, or receive information that you have requested. 
  * To send you email notifications as they pertain to your account, site updates, and upcoming events. 
  * To allow you to apply for a job 

Additionally:

  * We will not sell, share, rent, or trade your individual information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. 
  * We will maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and it will only be used to support your relationship with Alta Colleges. 
  * We may disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. 
  * We may disclose your personal information if Alta Colleges is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 
  * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sending out email communications on our behalf or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

If you submit a review:

We may use your review content in a number of different ways, including publicly displaying it, reformatting it, incorporating it into advertisements and other works, creating derivative works from it, promoting it, distributing it, and allowing others to do the same in connection with their own websites and media platforms. As such, you hereby irrevocably grant us world-wide, perpetual, non-exclusive, royalty-free, assignable, sublicensable, transferable rights to use your review content for any purpose. Please note that you also irrevocably grant the users of this website the right to access your review content in connection with their use of the website. Finally, you irrevocably waive, and cause to be waived, against Westwood and its users any claims and assertions of moral rights or attribution with respect to your review content. By "use" we mean use, copy, publicly perform and display, reproduce, distribute, modify, translate, remove, analyze, commercialize, and prepare derivative works of your content.

Personally identifiable information about yourself that you submit in your review will be available for viewing by users of this web site. Please do not include personally identifiable information about others in your post without their permission.

### Email Communications

We will send you strictly related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your email address. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

If you sign up to receive emails regarding upcoming events (such as an open house) you may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of emails by contacting us at [information@westwood.edu](mailto:information@westwood.edu) or by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or deactivate it by logging into your account if you are a registered student and updating your settings, filling out the request info form again, or by contacting us at [information@westwood.edu](mailto:information@westwood.edu).

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [information@westwood.edu](mailto:information@westwood.edu). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Testimonials/Videos

We post graduate testimonials and videos on our website which contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonials and videos to post their name along with their testimonials and videos. To request removal of your personal information or video from our site, contact us at [information@westwood.edu](mailto:information@westwood.edu). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Job Applications

When using our job application page(s), these pages are hosted by our third party service provider. The information we collect on these pages is name, email, phone number, work history, certificates, work licenses that you have obtained, and education. We will also collect the name and email address of your references. All information collected on these pages is covered by the Alta Colleges privacy policy. Our service provider has no access or control over this information, they are simply hosting the pages on our behalf. We use this information to contact you if we determine that you are eligible for the job you have applied for.

### Information collected automatically

In addition to the information you provide to us when you request information, we may automatically collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include:

  * Your Internet browser. 
  * Your IP address. 
  * Your computer's operating system. 
  * Your navigation path, including the domain name of the website that linked you to our site and which of our pages you visited. 
  * When you view one of our web sites, we may store cookies on your computer. These cookies allow us to tailor a web site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers you can block cookies, receive a warning about cookies, or erase all cookies from your hard drive. Please refer to your browser instructions or Help screen to learn more about these functions. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 
  * The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 
  * Our third party tracking utility company employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that helps us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 
  * Targeted or Behavioral Advertising:  
Targeted advertising (also known as Behavioral Advertising) uses information collected on an individual's web browsing behavior such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is then used to select which Alta College advertisement should be displayed to a particular individual on websites other than an Alta Colleges site. For example, if you have shown a preference for nursing while visiting Alta Colleges.com, you may be served an advertisement from Alta Colleges.com for nursing related programs when you visit a site other than Alta Colleges.com. The information collected is only linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising either comes from an Alta Colleges site or through third party website publishers. If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising from Alta Colleges that occurs when visiting our third party advertising publishers, please [click here](http://preferences.truste.com/truste/ "TRUSTe opt-out"). Please note that this will opt you out of targeted ads from Alta Colleges and any other participating advertisers. If you opt out, you will continue to receive online advertising from Alta Colleges; however, these ads may not be as relevant to you.
  * Web Analytics Tools:   
Our web sites use Google Analytics and Yahoo! Web Analytics to analyze web site use and activity. These tools use web-beacons and cookies to capture data about visitors to the web site. Your web browser sends this data to Google and/or Yahoo! as part of your interaction with the web site. The data typically includes the time spent viewing the website and any links or images on these pages that are clicked on. The cookies used by Google and/or Yahoo! contain no personal details such as your name, age or telephone number. Google and/or Yahoo! may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law. If you prefer not to have these web site analytics tools collect data about your web site visit, you may: (1) Install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) in your browser, which prevents Google Analytics from collecting information about your visits to our web sites; and (2) [Follow this link](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm) to opt out of data collection by Yahoo! Web Analytics.

### Westwood College Success Sites

The photos and information listed on these sites were provided by the students themselves along with granted permission to post the photos and the information on these sites. If you are one of these students and you choose to at any time have this information removed from these sites, please contact us at 1-877-691-5700.

Users of these sites are also able to share students' profiles on their Facebook wall. If you click on the “share” button located at the bottom of each profile you will be redirected to Facebook where you will be asked to submit. If any of our users wish to not allow other users of the site to share their profile on Facebook they may contact us at 1-877-691-5700 to request that we remove the “share” button from their profile.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

When you enter sensitive information (such as social security number) on our registration forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### Links to Other Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will leave the Alta Colleges site you are visiting and be redirected to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as Alta Colleges. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to a Alta Colleges site, you should read that site’s privacy policy before providing any personally identifiable information.

### How We Respond to Browser "Do Not Track" Signals: 

Some web browsers incorporate a "Do Not Track" feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. California law requires that website operators disclose how they respond to a Do Not Track signal and whether other third parties may collect personally identifiable information about an individual’s online activities from their site or service. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” signals. As the technology and communication between browser and website improves, we may make changes to our policy. Please refer to the section titled “Information Collected Automatically” for additional information.

### Changes in this Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or would like to have your personally identifiable information modified or deleted from our records, please email or call us. 

Alta Colleges Inc.   
10249 Church Ranch Way  
Westminster, CO 80021  
303-846-1700

Effective: 01/06/2014
